boscovs.com 2017-01-07

# Boscov’s Privacy Policy

Boscov’s Privacy Policy
Last Updated: June 2015
Welcome to Boscov’s. At Boscov’s we respect our customers and understand that you are concerned
about privacy. Earning and keeping your trust is important to us – therefore we take the protection and
proper use of your personal information seriously. In order to earn and keep your trust, we want you to
understand what personally identifiable information we collect, how we use such information and your
choices regarding how we use this information.
Our Policy Outlines:
    Why and how we collect your personal information;
    How we use and protect your personal information;
    With whom and when we share your personal information; and
    The choices you can make about how we collect, use, and share your personal information.
What Does Our Privacy Policy Include?
Our Policy covers how and why we collect, use, protect, and share your personal information at:
    Boscov’s retail stores, and
    On our websites where this Policy is posted.
Our Privacy Policy focuses on personal information – information that identifies you or reasonably can be
linked to information that identifies you. For example, when you buy an item that requires in-home
delivery or place an order online, we collect personal information, such as name, address, email address,
phone number, and credit or debit card information.
How Do We Hold Ourselves Accountable?
We require our employees, vendors, and service providers to manage your personal information
properly. We have designated specific employees who are responsible for helping to ensure compliance
with this Privacy Policy. We require all those who have access to or manage our customers’ personal
information to do so properly and in accordance with applicable laws and regulations and our policies.
What Type of Information Do We Collect?
We collect two types of information: information we receive from you; and information we receive from
others. Information we receive from you includes information you share with us, such as when you create
an account on one of our websites. This includes information you provide us through technology, such as
through a cookie placed on your computer when you visit our websites. We also receive information from
other sources to help us augment our records, personalize our service to you, and detect fraud. We try to
limit the information we collect to information needed to support our business.
Information We Receive From You
You share information with us in various ways in our Stores and Online. For example, you share

 information when you:
    Make an in-store or online purchase, or other transaction, with us;
    Create an account on one of our websites;
    Use a gift registry;
    Conduct a transaction or request a service where we collect information (including when required by
     law, such as hunting and fishing licenses);
    Request customer service or contact us;
    Post a review or comment on one of our social media pages, or post a rating, review or other user-
     generated content on one of our websites; and
    Participate in a contest, sweepstake, promotion, or survey.
 When you engage in these activities, you may share different types of personal information with us, such
 as your name, email address, physical or postal address, phone number, date of birth, and payment
 information.
 You also provide us information in other ways through technology. Some of this information may be linked
 to you personally. This information helps our websites work correctly and supports our analytics and
 customer marketing programs. Here are some examples of how technology may be used to provide
 information:
    Device Information: We may collect technical information when you visit our websites. This may
     include information such as Internet Protocol (IP) address, the type of mobile device you use, your
     device operating system and browser type, a unique device identifier, the address of a referring
     websites, the path you take through our websites, and other information about your session on our
     websites.
    Browsing Information: We may use technologies such as cookies, web beacons, and mobile device
     identifiers to collect information about the use of our websites. Cookies allow us to provide you
     relevant information as you use or return to our sites. Web beacons allow us to know if a certain page
     was visited, an email was opened, or if ad banners on our websites and other sites were effective. We
     use these tools to provide a continuous and more personalized shopping experience for you.
    Location Information: We may collect information about your location when your device is set to
     provide location information. For example, your device’s GPS signal may allow us identify the
     Boscov’s stores nearest to your location.
    Cameras: We operate cameras in store for security and operational purposes, for example, to help us
     improve the design of our stores to better serve our customers.
 Information We Receive From Other Sources
 We receive information about you from other sources to help us correct or supplement our records,
 improve the quality or personalization of our service to you, and prevent or detect fraud.
 How Do We Use Your Personal Information?
 We use your personal information to offer and provide you products and services and to support our
 business functions. These business functions include order and service fulfillment, internal business
 processes, marketing, authentication, loss and fraud prevention, public safety and legal functions. Some
 examples include:

    To fulfill your requests for products and services and communicate with you about those requests;
    To register and service your account;
    To administer contests, sweepstakes, promotions, and surveys;
    To provide customer service and alert you to product information;
    To help us personalize our service offerings, websites, and advertising;
    To help us improve your experience in our stores and through our websites;
    To send you information about our products, services, and promotions;
    To respond to reviews, comments, or other feedback you provide us; and
    To protect the security and integrity of our websites, and our business.
 To do this, we combine personal and non-personal information, collected online and offline, including
 information from third party sources. We also transfer or share your personal information within our
 corporate family of companies as permitted by law.
 How Do We Share Your Personal Information Outside of
 Boscov’s?
 We may share your personal information for various purposes, such as to conduct our business, when
 legally required, or with your consent; for example when you enter a sweepstakes or other promotion. We
 will not share your personal information outside of our corporate family of companies, except in the
 following circumstances:
 Vendors and Service Providers
 We share personal information about you with vendors and service providers that help with our business
 activities, including shipping vendors, payment card processors, and companies that help us improve our
 products and services such as suppliers who provide direct fulfillment services for certain products. We
 require our vendors and service providers to keep your personal information secure. We do not allow our
 vendors and service providers to use or share your personal information for any purpose other than
 providing their services in support of our business processes. Your personal information may be stored
 and processed by our vendors and service providers in the United States or other locations where the
 service providers or Boscov’s have facilities.
 Products and Services Offered by Other Businesses
 We will sometimes enable other businesses to make products or services available to our customers,
 such as through boscovs.com’s supplier direct fulfillment process. We indicate such products by noting
 that the product is “available online only”.
 Legal Requirements and Protection of Our Company and Others
 We may share your personal information in other special circumstances, which include situations when
 sharing is required by law, or we believe sharing will help to protect the safety, property, or rights of
 Boscov’s, our customers, our employees, or other persons. Examples include:
    Protecting the health or safety of customers;
    Addressing crimes committed on Boscov’s property;
    Identifying and addressing fraud or financial risk;
    Providing personal information from cameras to law enforcement at their request;
    Responding to a search warrant or other valid legal inquiry; and
    Responding to an investigative body in the case of a breach of an agreement or violation of law.

Business Transfers
In the event that all or a part of our business is merged, sold or reorganized (including transfers made as
a part of insolvency or bankruptcy proceedings), personal information about you may be shared with the
successor business.
With Your Consent
In any circumstance other than those described above, where you have not affirmatively opted out of
such sharing, we may share your personal information outside of our corporate family of companies, and
we also may sell or rent your some or all of personal information subject to our compliance with
applicable law.
What are Your Choices?
We want to offer you choices about the different ways we collect, use, or share your personal information.
These choices are described below.
Marketing Preferences
When we send marketing communications to you, we use the following standards:
We use an opt-out standard for phone and text messages and for sharing personal information with
companies outside our corporate family of companies for their use in direct marketing, such as sending
you promotions; and for email or for other communications, such as postal mail. Opt-out means we may
contact you, but will stop upon your request (as described below).
These standards may not apply to Boscov’s-branded credit card offerings because these are provided
through financial institutions that are not controlled by Boscov’s. However, you can choose to stop
receiving certain prescreened offers of credit that originate from participating nationwide credit reporting
agencies, including our prescreened offers, by calling the official Consumer Credit Reporting Industry
organization at 1-888-567-8688 or by going to www.optoutprescreen.com.
You can provide us with your marketing preferences by sending an email to
privacymanager@boscovs.com or by sending a letter to:
Boscov’s Department Store, LLC
Attn: Privacy Manager
4500 Perkiomen Ave.
Reading, PA 19606
If you contact us by email or mail, please be sure to include your full name, the types of communications
you would like to receive or not receive, and your related contact information. For instance, if you would
like to opt-out of mail, include your mailing address. Please allow sufficient time for your marketing
preferences to be processed. It may take up to ten days to process your requests related to email and up
to 30 days to process your requests related to telephone calls, text messages, and sharing information
with your consent. Please note that postal mailings are often prepared many weeks in advance, and you
may continue to receive mail for six to ten weeks.
Since we do not accept opt-out requests from third parties, such as catalog opt-out services, (other than
the provider of our private label credit card program), please communicate your request directly to us
through one of the mechanisms mentioned above.
Please know that, even if you opted out of receiving marketing communications from us, we may still
contact you for transactional or informational purposes. Some examples are contacts for customer

service, product information, service or reminder notices, or customer surveys. We may also need to
contact you with questions or information regarding your order.
Interest-Based Advertising Preferences
We personalize your experience on our websites by showing you advertisements that are tailored to your
interests. For example, if you browse or shop for dresses with us or on other sites, we may show you ads
for dresses as you continue to browse the Internet.
We show you advertisements related to Boscov’s or our advertising partners. We use third party
marketing companies that may use ad networks that may use your browsing history across participating
websites and mobile services to show you interest-based advertisements. You may also see ads for
Boscov’s on participating websites and mobile services based on how you browse. We may share
personal information about you with companies that advertise on our websites without your consent.
To opt out of interest-based advertising from Boscov’s, use the following mechanisms:
    Opt out through website specific mechanisms. Some websites, such as Facebook, offer their own
     opt out methods. Please refer to the website that you are visiting for additional information.
    Browser-based opt outs. Some internet browsers (e.g. Internet Explorer, Firefox, Chrome) offer
     their own opt-outs for interest-based advertising. The ad networks and ad service providers we
     participate with may not recognize these opt-outs.
    Mobile opt outs. Mobile devices offer their own opt-outs for interest-based advertising. Please refer
     to your device settings and instructions for additional information.
    If you choose to opt out of interest-based advertising, you will continue to see ads on our websites
     and other sites, but they will not be based on how you browse or shop at Boscov’s
    In the future, some of our mobile services may use your device’s location information. You can adjust
     the settings of your mobile device at any time to control whether your device communicates this
     location information. See your device instructions to learn more about these settings. In addition, we
     may offer you controls on our use of your mobile location information.
Please note – below are some common tips for managing your browsing experience on Boscov’s
websites and other websites in general. This information is provided for your convenience:
    To successfully opt out, you must have cookies enabled in your web browser (see your browser’s
     instructions for information on cookies and how to enable them).
    Opting out only applies to your current web browser on your current computer. If you use multiple
     computers or multiple web browsers, you must opt out on each one.
    Once you opt out, if you delete your browser’s saved cookies, you will need to opt out again.
How Do You Access and Update Your Personal
Information?
We provide you with various ways to update your personal information, including contact and account
information. We also take reasonable steps to keep your personal information accurate and
complete. You can update your personal information, including contact or account information, in the
following ways:

    If you have created an account on one of our websites, log into your account. Once you do, you will be
     able to enter and update your own contact information, as well as contact information for recipients
     you have designated.
    Contact us through one of the ways listed in the “Contact Us” section at the bottom of this Policy.
     Please include your current contact information, the information you are interested in accessing, and
     your requested changes. We will provide you the personal information requested if it is reasonably
     available, unless it infringes on the privacy of other individuals, and subject to reasonable limitations
     provided by law and internal procedures. Otherwise we will describe the types of information we
     typically collect. We will make the changes you request, or will provide an explanation of what actions
     we will be able to take with regard to the request.
    If you need to access your personal information related to a specified service provided to you by a
     Boscov’s service provider or business partner, we will refer you to the service provider or business
     partner. Please contact us via the “Contact Us” section below.
 How Do We Secure Your Personal Information?
 We recognize the importance of maintaining the security of our customers’ personal information. We use
 reasonable security measures, including physical, administrative, and technical safeguards to protect
 your personal information.
 We have employees who are responsible for helping to protect the security of your information. Whether
 you are shopping on our websites or in our stores, we use reasonable security measures, including
 physical, administrative, and technical safeguards. These measures may include security access controls
 or other physical security safeguards, information security technologies, and policies and procedures to
 help ensure the appropriate disposal of information, and training programs.
 Here are some examples of security measures we use to protect your personal information:
    Passwords are required to access your online account and help to protect your account
     information. Please keep this password confidential.
    Encryption technology, called Secure Sockets Layer (SSL), helps to protect personal information in
     certain areas of our websites during transport across the Internet. The presence of SSL encryption
     may be indicated by https in the browser URL or the image of a closed lock or solid key in the browser
     window. These indications may not be present in mobile services that use SSL.
    For payment card information, we use secured networks, encryption or other protection of cardholder
     data, physical and technical access controls, monitoring and tests of security systems, and other
     information security practices to help to protect your information.
 To learn more about measures you can take to protect the security of your personal information, check
 out these links for additional tips on making online shopping safe:
         Consumer tips for safe shopping online (Yahoo)
         You Are Here (FTC)
         How to shop online more safely (Microsoft)
         Safeshopping.org (American Bar Association)
         Help protect your privacy in online communities (Microsoft)
         How to limit your personal data in online directories (Microsoft)
         Privacy Consumer Toolbox (Better Business Bureau)

How Does Boscov’s Protect the Privacy of Children?
We recognize the importance of protecting children's online privacy. Our websites are intended for a
general audience and are not directed to children. In order to protect the privacy of children, Boscov’s
websites do not knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of 13. Please contact
us if you believe we may have collected information from your child through our websites or mobile
services and we will work to delete it.
Who Can I Contact at Boscov’s About the Privacy Policy?
You can contact the Boscov’s Privacy Manager online or by postal mail at the addresses below:
privacymanager@boscovs.com
Boscov’s Department Store, LLC
Attn: Privacy Manager
4500 Perkiomen Ave.
Reading, PA 19606
What Are Your California Privacy Rights?
Our Privacy Policy describes how we share information for marketing purposes. The Privacy Policy and
rights apply to all customers, including California residents.
California Privacy Rights
Pursuant to Section 1798.83 of the California Civil Code, residents of California have the right to request
from a business, with whom the California resident has an established business relationship, certain
information with respect to the types of personal information the business shares with third parties for
direct marketing purposes by such third party and the identities of the third parties with whom the
business has shared such information during the immediately preceding calendar year. Boscov ’s
websites do not have the ability to honor “do not track” requests. To request a copy of the information
disclosure provided by Boscov’s pursuant to Section 1798.83 of the California Civil Code, please contact
PrivacyManager@Boscovs.com.
How Will I Know if this Policy Changes?
We will post the date our Policy was last updated at the top of the Privacy Policy.
